@Qbank = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What does 1 + 1 equal?",
    ans: "2"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What does 5 * 6 equal?",
    ans: "30"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What does 4-1 equal?",
    ans: "3"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What does 6 / 2 equal?",
    ans: "3"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What does 4 * 4 equal?",
    ans: "16"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What does 10 + 5 equal?",
    ans: "15"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What does 20 * 5 equal?",
    ans: "100"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What does 90 / 2 equal?",
    ans: "45"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What does 15 * 4 equal?",
    ans: "60"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What does 19 - 2 equal?",
    ans: "17"
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "What does 8 + 7 equal?",
    ans: "15"
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "What does 78 / 3 equal?",
    ans: "26"
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "What does 100 * 100 equal?",
    ans: "10000"
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "What does 321 + 123 equal?",
    ans: "444"
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "What does 937 - 268 equal?",
    ans: "669"
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "What does 4000 - 1500 equal?",
    ans: "2500"
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "What does 898 * 2 equal?",
    ans: "1796"
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "What does 12 * 12 equal?",
    ans: "144"
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "What does 99 / 11 equal?",
    ans: "9"
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "What does 3000 / 5 equal?",
    ans: "600"
  }
  
]